wheretogetengaged.com 2010-05-31

# WTGE Privacy Policy

The following information describes our privacy policy and how your personal information is handled on this site. This policy applies to information provided by you in the registration process. This policy does not apply to information provided by you to vendors and/or advertisers on this site. You should consult the individual policies of those vendors and/or advertisers to determine how information you provide will be handled by them.

By accepting the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy when registering, you expressly agree to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this policy.

### Providing of Personal Information

Individuals may browse this website without revealing any personal information. However, once you provide us with personal information, that information is transferred and stored on our servers in the United States.

PLEASE BE AWARE that when you post material, comments, messages, photos, videos, etc. on this site, from a privacy standpoint, you are doing so at your own risk. While WTGE may provide you with privacy options that are intended to limit access by others to your community page(s), to those you choose, those options are sometimes imperfect, and therefore WTGE cannot and does not guarantee that your posts or other communication will not be viewed by unauthorized individuals.

When you register with us, or provide other information, the information provided by you is gathered from your browser using “cookies”, or pieces of data stored on your computer which are tied to information about you. These cookies terminate when you close your browser. WTGE does not store these cookies; however, at your option you may create a persistent cookie that stores your user name, but not your password, to ease your access to WTGE.

### Use of Information

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, efficient and entertaining online environment. With that in mind, you agree that WTGE may use your personal information to:

  * provide the services and support you request;
  * provide you with information about our services, updates to those services, and advise you of promotional offers based on the information you provide;
  * resolve disputes, collect account fees, and provide online support based on your needs;
  * customize and improve our services and offerings;
  * limit the potential for illegal activity, prevent potentially harmful conduct, and enforce our Terms of Use.

### Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose your personal information in response to appropriate legal process, to enforce the Terms of Use of this site, or in response to claims that a posting or other content violates the rights of others, or where disclosure of such information may be reasonably necessary to protect the rights of others, all of which will be only be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws. WTGE will not disclose your personal identity to third parties unless required to do so by applicable law, under appropriate legal processes.

Please remember that your User ID may be displayed onsite and is connected to your activity on this site. If you associate your name with your User ID, individuals who know your name will be able to identify your online activity. If you share a computer, or other internet access with others, your personal information may also be visible to those individuals.

WTGE takes reasonable and appropriate steps and precautions to protect your personal information. We cannot guarantee the privacy or security of your information. Please remember email and instant messaging are not generally recognized as secure forms of communication. WTGE encourages you to carefully evaluate and consider who you share information with, and the privacy policies, if any, of others before sharing your information.

As a member of the WTGE community, we ask that you act responsibly while enjoying this site. If you notice any unusual activity on this site, which, if left unchecked may interfere with the rights of other community members, or which may be of an abusive, threatening, or criminal nature, you are encouraged to immediately report such activity to us at [tou@wheretogetengaged.com](mailto:tou@wheretogetengaged.com).

### Account Responsibility

It is your responsibility to take reasonable steps to protect your personal information and the information connected with your account. When establishing a password for your account, we encourage you to use unique characters, letters, and numbers. We also encourage you not to disclose that information to third parties. WTGE will not ask you for your password. If you lose control of your password, you may effectively lose control of your account and you may become liable for legally binding actions taken by third parties on your account. In the event your password has been revealed to others, you should immediately notify us and change your password.

In the event you discover that any of your personal information has been compromised, you should, again immediately notify us. With your assistance, we will then take appropriate measures to protect that information from further disclosure.

### Amendments

This Privacy Policy may be amended at any time by the posting of amended terms on this site. Minor amendments may be made without notice, while amendments of material terms, unless otherwise stated, shall become effective on the 31st day after their initial posting. You may send your comments, questions or concerns about any amendments, or about our Privacy Policy to [tou@wheretogetengaged.com](mailto:tou@wheretogetengaged.com).
